

MAXIM (PETROVICH) KOSEY

Java Backend Engineer/Developer

Location: Kryvyi Rih, Ukraine

Phone/Viber/WhatsApp/Telegram: +380 67 759 63 11

Spare Phone: +380 63 290 20 06
Skype: live:.cid.3f50320b2dd42fa1
E-mail: koseymax@gmail.com
GitHub: https://github.com/Max11mus

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/maxim-kosey-a24747248



DATE OF BIRTH

Aug 04, 1979

NATIONALITY

Ukrainian

HARD SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, SQL, HTML, CSS, Python, C++, VBA, 1C 7.7, FoxPro, x86 Intel Assembler

Web Technologies:

RESTful APIs, JSON, XML

Java Frameworks:

Spring, Hibernate

Testing Frameworks:

JUnit, Mockito, Testconainers

Build Tools:

Maven

Database Systems:

PostgreSQL, Microsoft SQL Server, Interbase, Btrieve Pervasive SQL

Database Migration:

Flyway

Version Control Systems:

Git

Containerization:

Docker

Operating Systems:

Microsoft Windows, Ubuntu/Debian, Novell NetWare, MS-DOS/PC-DOS

Network Devices:

Cisco IOS, OpenWrt, Microtik RouterOS

HUMANS LANGUAGES

English - B1

Ukrainian – Native Speaker

Russian - Native Speaker

Profile

Developed and Maintained Enterprise-Level JAVA Applications using Spring Framework and Maven Build Tool, Ensuring Efficient and Scalable Software Solutions.

Utilized Docker for Containerization, Enabling Consistent Deployment across Multiple Environments and Simplifying the Deployment Process.

Designed and Implemented RESTful APIs to Integrate the Application with External Systems, Resulting in Enhanced Functionality and Improved User Experience.

Employment History

Sole Proprietor (FOP 3 Group), Self Employed – 2002 - 2023

Development of "UMS - University Management System" with SpringBoot, Maven, JUnit, Mockito, PostgreSQL, RESTful API, Flyway, Git, Docker in 2022-2023 (https://github.com/Max11mus/UMS---University-Management-System)

Programming with Excel VBA and 1C:Enterprise 7.7 @ Microsoft SQL Server in 2002 - 2014

Configuration and Repair of Computer, Network (**OpenWrt, Microtik RouterOS**), and Office Equipment (2002 - 2023)

Typography Design and Printing with Using Computer Software: **CorelDRAW**, **Adobe Illustrator**, **Microsoft Word in 2002 – 2023**

Founder, LLC "PRIME ELECTRIC" - 2019 - 2023

Development of Electrical Engineering Projects with Using **AutoCad** and other CAD Software (2019 - 2023)

Head of the Group in Electrical Engineering Department – 2017 - 2019

Leading, Managing and Mentoring the Group of 3 Design Engineers

Development of Electrical Engineering Projects with Using **AutoCad** and other CAD Software

Design Engineer in Electrical Engineering Department, State Institute for Enterprise Design in the Mining Industry "KryvbasProject" – 2004 - 2017

Development of Electrical Engineering Projects with Using **AutoCad** and other CAD Software

Development of a desktop applications for electrical calculations using **Borland C++ Builder @ Excel VBA in 2004 - 2008**

System Administrator, Pension Fund of Ukraine - 2001 - 2002

Maintenance of a Network of 100 Computers and a Client-server Software System ASOPD: **Btrieve Pervasive SQL** Database Server under **Novell Netware**, Clients under Windows 98 in DOS Mode

Development of Applications for Generating and Printing Reports with FOXPRO for DOS

Schoolboy, Kryvyi Rih Gymnasium No. 95 – 1994 - 1995

Development of the Device for Pairing "ACPU SM-6315" (Soviet Fast Drum-Type Printer Produced by NPO "ELECTRONMASH") with an IBM-compatible PC under MS-DOS: the Hardware Part Converts Electrical Signals from the IFSP Interface to the

SOFT SKILLS

Strong problem-solving and analytical skills

Excellent communication and collaboration abilities

Detail-oriented and committed to delivering high-quality code

Centronics Interface; the Software Part Represents a Driver Written with Intel X86-Assembler for MS-DOS, Converts Symbols from KOI-7 Code Page to ASCII 8-bit Code Page

Education

Master's Degree Diploma **«Computer Engineering»** - Kryvyi Rih National University – 2022 - Present

Master's Degree Diploma **«Electromechanical Systems Automation and Electric Drive»** - Kryvyi Rih National University – 1996 – 2001

Middle School Diploma with Specialization in **Mathematics** - Kryvyi Rih Gymnasium No. 95 - 1990 - 1996

Courses

JAVA SPRING MENTORING COURSE - FOXMINDED.UA - #22120260 27.12.2022

CCNA 7: SWITCHING, ROUTING, AND WIRELESS ESSENTIALS - Cisco Networking Academy - 06.02.2023

Certificate of Responsible Executor - Chief Project Engineer (CPE) - <u>Guild of Designers</u> in <u>Construction</u> - AP 015476 26.04.2019

Hobbies

Learning Foreign Languages: Actively learning English to enhance cross-cultural communication skills.

Data Science: Passionate about data analysis, visualization, and machine learning algorithms.

Al & Neural Networks: Fascinated by artificial intelligence, particularly neural networks.





